<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on TechAware</title>
    <link>https://techaware.netlify.app/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on TechAware</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 18:31:55 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://techaware.netlify.app/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Web Dev Resources</title>
      <link>https://techaware.netlify.app/posts/web-dev-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 18:31:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techaware.netlify.app/posts/web-dev-resources/</guid>
      <description>Collection of useful resources available on the Internet related to Blockchain career.
Learn these basic things which will tell you how to place content on web page and later style it so it looks better:
 HTML Crash Course For Absolute Beginners CSS Crash Course For Absolute Beginners  Now learn Bootstrap. It is a CSS library. But it is not as complex as it sounds. Just a bunch of CSS code which is commonly used in all sites, so we include it using CDN link and save our time :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Resources</title>
      <link>https://techaware.netlify.app/posts/blockchain-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 08:51:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techaware.netlify.app/posts/blockchain-resources/</guid>
      <description>Collection of useful resources available on the Internet related to Blockchain career.
If you do not have a practical idea of how blockchain works, here is a basic implementation of it in JavaScript you can follow on YouTube by Simple Explained:
 Creating a blockchain Implementing Proof-of-Work Mining rewards &amp;amp; transactions Signing transactions  To be continued &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Security Resources</title>
      <link>https://techaware.netlify.app/posts/cybersecurity-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 08:40:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techaware.netlify.app/posts/cybersecurity-resources/</guid>
      <description>Collection of useful resources available on the Internet related to Cyber Security career.
General  The Career Media Resources Web Vulnerabilities Learn &amp;amp; Practice  Bug Bounty  What is it really? Hunting Methodology Popular Tools Burp Suite App Practice Hacking Skills Write ups Reporting Bugs  Capture The Flags  The Beginner Guide Calender of All Events Popular Tools List  Penetration Testing  Guide To Method OSCP Certification Practice Penetration LinkedIn Jobs  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Burp Suite Professional for free on Windows</title>
      <link>https://techaware.netlify.app/posts/2020-09-06-burp-suite-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 21:19:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techaware.netlify.app/posts/2020-09-06-burp-suite-pro/</guid>
      <description>Burp Suite is an integrated platform for performing security testing of web applications. It is designed to be used by hands-on testers to support the testing process. Here we will see how you can install it for free on your Windows 7/8/10 64-bit machine.
Things that you will need:
 Java JDK (13.0.2) - Download Burp Suite Pro zip file (2021.10) - Download   After you have downloaded both the files, follow these steps:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
